i began my career as a journalist about
1984. you know early on in my career
i worked very hard i was very diligent i
kept long hours
i read a lot especially
researching on the stories that i was
assigned to because the challenge in the
early years was to improve my craft and
build credibility
[Music]
in the beginning i was open to a lot of
opportunities and challenges
without being so conscious about the
pain knowing that payback would come
later
success doesn't happen overnight
but over time
[Music]
you know after i lost my job of over 30
years pivoting to a new venture just
like provencana was easier because i was
financially prepared and had a backup
plan sound financial planning will grow
and protect what you build
fwd manifest gives you strong life
protection
and smart wealth investment and because
it has protection and investment
components you can manifest your dreams
with more confidence and less worries
[Music]
i will be giving greater focus to
farming in the second half of 2022 aside
from growing all the things that
provencana needs i want to eventually
live there the aim is really to be able
to go back to basic
and to tap the healing and nurturing
properties of philippine endemic plan
for me the secret to success is enjoying
what you do
and also to save our life's little
pleasures don't forget to celebrate
living
i manifested my dreams and i know you
can too invest
and manifest your future
with fwd manifest